Austin J Henry

Grants Pass, OR

■ github.com/KingAusti ■ linkedin.com/in/kingaustinhenry ■ Cell: (541)499-4420

■ info@austinhenry.dev

Summary

Seasoned IT Tech with more than 7 years of experience in the fast-paced Technology Sector. Excellent Sales and Computer Technology skills. Track record of achieving exceptional results in Networking and HelpDesk.

Skills

Critical Thinking Computers and Electronics Customer and Personal Service Active Listening Complex Problem Solving Time Management

Experience

IT Support Analyst II, 04/2019 to Present Dutch Bros. Coffee - Grants Pass, OR

- 1. Support the IT Operations of the company by responding to incoming support requests along with proactively working to improve systems to improve performance and stability.
- 2. Utilize tools, processes, training, communication and team collaboration to ensure the company can stay focused on serving our customers.
- 3. Provide second level support for escalated issues, work with other teams as needed, train/mentor other staff and work towards improving the overall functionality of IT related systems.

Key Accomplishments

- Played a pivotal role in implementation of a new network hardware solution, allowing for immediate scaled growth of our company footprint.
- Co-piloted setup of satellite HQ in Portland, OR allowing for employees located in our Portland area to have a comfortable and secure office to work from.
- Setup and managed IT infrastructure at Portland COACHA 2019, a week long event of 5000(Half of the company at the time) Dutch Bros employees coming together to celebrate the company and our culture.
- Coordinated setup and testing of both Oregon State and University of Oregon booths, while maintaining state-mandated COVID protocols. This allowed students at both universities to have access to delicious drinks while at Ducks and Beavers games.

IT HelpDesk Technician, 09/2016 to 04/2019 Lithia Motors Inc. – Medford, OR

• Use computers for various applications, such as database management or word processing. Perform data backups and disaster recovery operations.

- Diagnose, troubleshoot, and resolve hardware, software, or other network and system problems, and replace defective components when necessary. Plan, coordinate, and implement network security measures to protect data, software, and hardware.
- Maintain and administer computer networks and related computing environments including computer hardware, systems software, applications software, and all configurations.

AppleCare Advisor, 07/2015 to 07/2016 Apple, Inc – Medford, OR

Answered phone calls from Customers needing assistance with all their Apple devices. Learned the importance of great customer service even in the most stressful of situations. Helped enrich the Customer's experience with Apple and created Promoters.

Consultation Agent, 06/2014 to 07/2015 Geek Squad – Medford, OR

Helped Clients solve a range of problems on assorted devices. Learned how to manage appointments and customer walk-ins with fluid ease.

Made Clients issues and problems with their new devices disappear. Kept a level head in a high stress, fast paced environment.

Sales Consultant, 10/2013 to 06/2014 Best Buy – Medford, OR

Sold computers and tablets during the busy holiday season. Learned the ins and outs of various sales techniques. Provided support to customers in need of help buying gifts for family and friends. Learned how to work with a team on the busiest black friday in recent memory.

Cashier/Sales Associate, 01/2012 to 01/2013 The Home Depot - Phoenix, OR

Guided customers to the appropriate departments. Assisted with the stocking and pricing of the store merchandise. Completed daily cleaning duties in store and back office.

Lead Generator, 07/2011 to 11/2011 The Home Depot – Canoga Park, Ca

Transitioned from ge ing leads for only HVAC systems to selling all of the At Home.

Lead Generator, 04/2011 to 07/2011 AG Air Inc – Van Nuys, Ca

Generated Leads for HVAC Systems in The Home Depot #0612 as a sales vendor. Learned the layout of the store and helped customers with anything they needed. The store manager was so pleased with my work that she brought me on as the store's official Lead Generator.

Executive Assistant/ Coater, 01/2010 to 06/2010 Specialized Coating Services – Fremont, CA

Worked on office projects using Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint. Answer telephone and routed calls to appropriate recipients. Coated circuit boards for tech. oriented companies. Files, faxes and photocopies documents as needed. Assisted clients as needed.

Drivers Helper, 11/2009 to 12/2009 UPS - Menlo Park, Ca

Assisted UPS driver in delivering packages during the busy holiday season. Learned essentials in

teamwork in a fast paced work environment

VOLUNTEER WORK

Certified Peer Visitor for Amputee Coalition of America June 2013 to Present

No one is potentially in a better position to understand about living life with an amputation or supporting a person with limb loss/difference than someone who has been there. An experienced, well-trained peer can offer encouragement and information from a place, and at a pace, that an individual in this circumstance can better absorb.

Education

Certificate of Completion: University of Oregon, Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

GED: General Education, Aug 2009 North Hills Prep School - Los Angeles, CA